The Amanda Seale Show.
It's time to get into my big up, big up.
All right, so today's big up goes to Target for endorsing Black Joy.
Let me tell you, we endorse Black Joy every Friday here at the Amanda Seale Show, by the way.
Literally every Friday we share a number of stories of Black Joy.
But Target dropped a popular clothing collection with the slogan, Black Joy is revolutionary.
Carlton McMackie, the creator of Black Men's Smile, said,
We believe that Black Joy is revolutionary because of all that it must resist
and the ways it must persist in order to simply exist.
Yes, my brother.
Now to let down goes to this white lady on the Instagrams.
No, she was on the Twitters.
And she was just upset about this.
She literally tweeted, Target is insufferable.
Had to do a return and can't wait to leave.
Man, Karen's draws was in a bunch.
She said, I can't stand happy little Black babies.
I can't.
A doubleheader let down.
Not to be on podcasts.
Run the name out.
If y'all want to hear my thoughts on Daryl Richardson, aka Little Scrappy,
then you're going to have to go to my Patreon.
Go to Patreon.com, type in my name, and you'll get what you are looking for,
which is really just something to distract you from the day.